{
  "title": "Airport and flight travel expressions",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Check-in counters are open two hours before the scheduled flight ........ time. ",
      "answers": ["going", "arrival", "departure", "transit"],
      "correct": "departure"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "It is the passenger's responsibility to ensure their ........ is valid for entry and they have fulfilled all immigration requirements in the country of destination.",
      "answers": ["endorsement", "passport", "document", "papers"],
      "correct": "passport"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Passengers are required to produce appropriate ........ at the check-in counter.  ",
      "answers": ["passport", "visa", "ticket", "identification"],
      "correct": "identification"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Passengers are advised to be at the ........ gate at least thirty minutes before the scheduled departure time of their flight.",
      "answers": ["boarding", "ticket", "departure", "arrival"],
      "correct": "boarding"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "If you fail to check in on time or fail to board the aircraft by the time the aircraft departs, the fare you paid will not be ........ to you for any reason whatsoever. ",
      "answers": ["returned", "remunerated", "refunded", "rewarded"],
      "correct": "refunded"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Children below age 12 will not be accepted for ........ unless they are accompanied by a person of at least 18 years of age.",
      "answers": ["journey", "voyage", "carriage", "trip"],
      "correct": "carriage"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Passengers are strongly ........ not to check in valuable and fragile items as baggage.",
      "answers": ["advised", "informed", "told", "reminded"],
      "correct": "advised"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Passengers are required to retrieve their ........ as soon as it is available for collection at their place of destination.",
      "answers": ["ticket", "baggage", "boarding pass", "passport"],
      "correct": "baggage"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "It is the passenger's responsibility to ........ all outgoing flights at least 72 hours prior to departure.",
      "answers": ["rebook", "reorder", "reserve", "reconfirm"],
      "correct": "reconfirm"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Passengers must ........ at the airport sufficiently in advance of the scheduled flight departure time to permit completion of government formalities and check-in procedures.",
      "answers": ["depart", "transit", "arrive", "transfer"],
      "correct": "arrive"
    }
  ]
}
